# AKSHAY BENNY

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Kerala, India

### **EDUCATION**

# B.TECH MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

Cochin University Of Science And Technology 2018 – 2022

# SECONDARY AND HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION

Assisi Vidyaniketan Public School Kakkanad 2003 – 2017

## SKILLS

- ReactJs
- NextJs
- Mongoose
- Express
- GraphQL
- Apollo Client
- Tailwind CSS
- React testing library
- Cypress
- Jest
- Redux-toolkit
- React recoil
- Figma

## INTERESTS

- Novels
- Comics
- Swimming
- Badminton



akshaybennyajh@mail.com

T +91 940026 1560

in LinkedIn

Github

Portfolio

# ABOUT

My name is Akshay Benny, a full-stack web developer who is dedicated to learning new things, specializes in building fast responsive web applications and a Mechanical Engineering graduate from Cochin University Of Science And Technology with background in UI designing.

# **PROJECTS**

#### **E-COMMERCE WEBSITE**

React, NodeJs, Express, Mongoose, Redux-toolkit, Razorpay

Users can sign into their account or log out, add products to cart and make payment. It includes additional features like pagination, search functionality and more.

#### PROJECT MANAGEMENT SYSTEM

React, Express, Mongoose, GraphQL, Apollo Client, Jest

A project management system in which we can add clients, add projects which are connected to the clients with CRUD functionality and user authentication.

### **TWITTER CLONE**

NextJs, Next-auth, Firebase, Recoil, Tailwind CSS

A clone of Twitter webapp with user authentication. Users can add or remove tweets, like or unlike tweets and add comment to a tweet.

## **GOOGLE CLONE**

NextJs, Google search API, Tailwind CSS

A clone of Google with server side rendering, integrated with Google search API in which users can search for anything and get responses in web and image categories with user authentication.

## EXPERIENCE

Full Web Developer Intern

July, 2021 - February 2022

Edureka, India

Hack Ambassador in Hack The Mountain 2.0

June 2021

Freelancer

January 2022 - May 2022